<xml>
	<!-- blank entry to copy -->
	<entry style="left">
		<title></title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<description>
			
		</description>
		<technology></technology>
		<url></url>
	</entry>

	<section title="experience">
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Shiver Entertainment</title>
			<subtitle>Unreal Engine Optimization Specialists</subtitle>
			<description>
				Used as a trusted contractor by several AAA studios, Shiver Entertainment is one of the foremost experts in optimizing Unreal Engine software to run on lower powered systems (particularly the Nintendo Switch).
				Despite having been acquired by Embracer Group by way of Saber Interactive, Shiver is perhaps most commonly known for their close working relationship with Warner Brothers Games and subsidiaries, with several major titles having their Switch ports done by Shiver.
			</description>
			<technology>Unreal Engine | C++ | Blueprint</technology>
			<url>https://www.shiver.net</url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Virtel</title>
			<subtitle>Virtual Reality Language Learning</subtitle>
			<description>
				Virtel was a small team working to create software for foreign language education in Virtual Reality.
				Although now defunct, the team was at one point poised to publish an initial package of Latin American Spanish learning environments and activities.
				</description>
			<technology>Virtual Reality | Unity | C#</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Mozenda</title>
			<subtitle>Commercial Web Scraping</subtitle>
			<description>
				Mozenda is a SaaS Web Scraping company based out of Utah.
				Clients contract an individual specialist to design and customize agents built using Mozenda's proprietary software, as well as data post-processing and formatting.
				</description>
			<technology>HTML/CSS | XML | JavaScript</technology>
			<url>https://www.mozenda.com/</url>
		</entry>
		
	</section>
	
	<section title="skills">
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Unreal Engine Development</title>
			<subtitle></subtitle>
			<description>
				With the success of Fortnite, Epic games has basically cemented their place in the gaming world as "One Engine/One Game".
				Good thing that Engine so powerful.
			</description>
			<technology>C++ | Blueprint Scripting | Python Integration | Program Structure</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Console Development</title>
			<subtitle></subtitle>
			<description>
				Console development adds just one more layer of complexity to everything else that needs to be considered when it comes to the development process.
				Fortunately once the hurdles are past, development is just as smooth as any other project (not smooth).
			</description>
			<technology>C++ | Console Profiling Tools | Cert Requirements</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>

		<entry style="left">
			<title>Embedded Systems</title>
			<subtitle></subtitle>
			<description>
				Very familiar with the C language, having worked with Arduino, the MSP430, and the PINQ board.
				Also includes (tangentially related) experience using FPGAs and building software defined processors.
				"I hope you're tired of Object Oriented Programming!"
			</description>
			<technology>C | Assembly | Verilog | Linux Drivers</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Algorithm Design</title>
			<subtitle></subtitle>
			<description>
				All of the different ways that difficult problems can be (at worst) solved and (at best) solved efficiently.
				Not always needed for a simple project, but always worth knowing.
			</description>
			<technology>Graphs | Sorting | Heuristics | "Big O" | Dynamic Programming</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>
	</section>

	<section title="projects">
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Hogwarts Legacy</title>
			<subtitle>"Yer a Skeletal Mesh, Harry"</subtitle>
			<description>
				Certainly the most Wizard-y game in recent memory; Hogwarts Legacy succeeded in bring ingthe Magical world to life in a way that other games can only dream of.
				I'm so tired of looking at robes.
			</description>
			<technology>Unreal | C++ | Python | SQL</technology>
			<url>https://www.hogwartslegacy.com/en-us</url>
		</entry>

		<entry style="left">
			<title>Mortal Kombat 1</title>
			<subtitle>"I don't think the model is wrong, that's just how the finishing move looks..."</subtitle>
			<description>
				Have you ever wondered: "What would happen if I punched that guy really hard in the neck?"
				Well, we have the answer!: He would die.
			</description>
			<technology>Unreal | C++ | Python | Maya</technology>
			<url>https://www.mortalkombat.com/en-us</url>
		</entry>

		<entry style="left">
			<title>Ongoing Work</title>
			<subtitle>[REDACTED]</subtitle>
			<description>
				Nothing to see here!
				Unless you're hiring/investing, then it's really cool and you should email me to talk about it!
			</description>
			<technology>Unreal | C++ | Python | AWS Gamelift | JavaScript</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Distraction Break</title>
			<subtitle>Time Management through Interruption</subtitle>
			<description>
				Distract break is a simple extension that allows you to build a list of distracting sites and configure a limiting timer.
				The app differentiates between time spent on productive sites and time spent on blacklisted ones, and increments the timer when more time is spent unproductively.
			</description>
			<technology>HTML/CSS | JavaScript | Chrome API</technology>
			<url>https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/distract-break/gnkddjnjkddnhdlokndnlfehpcahnfba?hl=en-US</url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Capstone Project</title>
			<subtitle>Self Aligning Free Space Optics</subtitle>
			<description>
				My Capstone project team was contracted by Raytheon to design and develop a system that would allow for easy self-alignment of a Free Space Optics (FSO) systems.
				By using Computer Vision and an Arduino micro controller we were able to create a system that could identify and pivot towards a target at distances of up to one Kilometer.
			</description>
			<technology>C++ | Python | Arduino | OpenCV</technology>
			<url></url>
		</entry>
		
		<entry style="left">
			<title>Food Wheel</title>
			<subtitle>For when your Friends are Unhelpful</subtitle>
			<description>
				This is a really simple page that uses your location data to pull a list of local restaurants and select one at random.
				There is a bit of customization if you want to limit some options, but it's very rudimentary.
				Perfect when nobody will agree on anything, because it will easily prove that your group can agree on what everybody DOESN'T want.
			</description>
			<technology>HTML/CSS | JavaScript</technology>
			<url>food_wheel.html</url>
		</entry>
	</section>
</xml>
